ultraseosolutions.com 2019-05-22

# Privacy Policy - SEO Solutions | SEO Services | SEO Packages

#### 2\. Collection and Use of Information

2CO collects personal information to set up and manage accounts for our ecommerce services and to handle orders of goods and services from 2CO.

You may need to provide 2CO with personal information such as:

  * names; phone numbers; mailing, billing, shipping, and email addresses;
  * bank account information; credit and debit card information; dates of birth; and identification documents.

2CO uses such information for:

  * website registration; enabling sales and other transactions; processing payments and settlement; sending payouts; handling orders; providing receipts;
  * providing customer service; providing dispute resolution, chargebacks, refunds, or related issues;
  * marketing and surveys; sending service update notices;
  * recovering debt and collections; detecting and preventing fraud; detecting and preventing violations of our legal agreements;
  * measuring, improving, and customizing our services; and
  * fulfilling other technical, logistical, financial, tax, legal, compliance, administrative, or back office functions.

2CO may also collect background information and credit checks from third parties to verify your identity; deter, detect, and prevent fraud and illegal activity; make business decisions; and as a part of our legal obligations. 2CO retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

##### Community Information

2CO collects information from you to post entries to our community website or forums. Such information may include your email address, Internet Protocol address, user name, date and time of signup, and date and time of posts to the forum.

2CO uses this information for the secure and efficient functioning of our website, to provide you with access to our community site, to detect and prevent violations of our legal agreements, and as part of any legal obligations related to our community website.

##### Transaction Information

2CO collects information on each transaction conducted through our website. Such information may include the amount of the transaction; the goods purchased; the identity of the seller, affiliate, and customer; payment type; currency; location; Internet Protocol address; and websites visited.

2CO uses such information for refunds, for customer service, for website optimization, or for other administrative or business purposes. 2CO may share information related to the transactions you conduct through our website with sellers, affiliates, or customers for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Statement. 2CO retains transaction information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

##### Customer Service Correspondence

2CO also collects information involving customer service correspondence. This information may include emails, internet chats, faxes, or telephone calls directed to our customer service centers. 2CO processes this information to provide customer service, handle complaints or disputes, measure and improve our customer service, detect and prevent fraud, and detect and prevent violations of our legal agreements. 2CO retains customer service information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

##### Cookies, Web Beacons, and Logs

2CO collects information related to your use of our website using cookies, web beacons, and log information.

Cookies are small files containing strings of text stored on your computer. 2CO uses cookies to authenticate you as a user when you log in, track your session, deliver content specific to your preferences and interests, store the contents of your shopping cart, provide features related to payment and customer service, and provide other functions.

Web beacons are objects embedded into web pages that allow us to determine whether and for how long users view web pages. We use web beacons for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, auditing and reporting, personalization, and other functions.

Log information may include web requests, Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type, browser language, date and time of your request, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 2CO uses this information to enhance the functionality of the website and to make your access more convenient, secure, and efficient.

2CO also uses information gathered from logs, cookies, and web beacons to monitor website performance; improve website design, functionality, and security; and assemble web analytics and activity trends. 2CO retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

You may stop your browser from accepting cookies or web beacons. The Help portion of your browser should explain how to configure your browser’s cookie handling. Your browser may have add-ons that may help you block web beacons. You may have limited functionality if you block cookies or web beacons set by our website.

##### HotJar

2CO uses HotJar, a web analytics service. HotJar uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help 2CO analyze how users use the site. You may find HotJar’s Privacy Policy at <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/gdpr-commitment>.

##### Google AdWords

2CO uses Google AdWords, a web analytics and search engine advertising campaign management service. Google AdWords uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help 2CO analyze how users use the site. You may find Google’s Privacy Statement at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html>.

##### Google Analytics

2CO uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help 2CO analyze how users use the site. You may find Google’s Privacy Policy at <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/gdpr-commitment>.

##### Marketo

2CO uses Marketo, an email distribution and web analytics service. Marketo uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help 2CO distribute emails analyze how users use the site. You may find Marketo’s Privacy Statement at <https://documents.marketo.com/legal/privacy/>.
